# Cyrulleann Vigil

# **Content Marketing Manager**

A creative and organized leader with over five years of experience in email communication and customer-obsessed content creation; able to design media effectively in Adobe Creative Suite and Articulate 360. Strives to motivate and support teams by supporting transparent communication, providing assistance when needed, and creating structured project plans to ensure timely delivery.

## Experience

○ Content Marketing Manager · 2022 - Present · Strike Visuals

Created cohesive brand style guide and standards to ensure communication consistency Increased email open rate 15% with segmented and targeted data in HubSpot Effected project management strategy reflected in content calendar and Trello

Training Developer • 2021 - 2022 • Marriott Vacation Club

Ensure brand voice and standards are adhered to across training modules

Draft copy, design module layout, and record narration for associate training

Audit over 30 existing training materials following introduction new processes or verbiage

O Digital Design Specialist · 2016 - 2021 · Marriott Vacation Club

Created over 200 email campaigns using CSS and HTML for Marriott Vacation Club resorts Work with resort representatives to construct customer-facing email and print collaterals Pull customer data, review test emails, and load data in Salesforce to execute email blasts

O Vacation Ownership Advisor • 2014 - 2016 • Marriott Vacation Club

Work with Owners and guests to establish future vacations using 4 different programs

Explain how to use timeshare programs effectively using clear and concise language

Ensure all information regarding loan balance, escrow, and payoff are accurately detailed

## Education

O University of Utah

2017-2019

Bachelor of Science - Psychology Graduation date: December, 2019

# Certifications

- O Content Marketing Certification HubSpot
- SEO Certification HubSpot
- Social Media Marketing Certification HubSpot
- Data Analysis Certification IBM

## Personal Data

## **Address**

572 W 1425 N, Unit U Layton, UT 84041

### **Phone**

(801) 867-1880

### **Email**

Cyrulleann@gmail.com

### **Portfolio**

Cyrulleann.org

## Key Skills

Analytical

Data-driven

Strong communication

Highly organized

Adaptable

Motivated

## Technical Skills

Articulate 360

Adobe Creative Suite

Microsoft 365

Copywriting

ADDIE/SAM models

Search Engine Optimization